Sahil Seta

CAREER OBJECTIVES

Around 3 years of experience working in a corporate environment as a Software developer.

JUNAGADH, GUJARAT,INDIA (362001)

+91 76001 22030

sahilseta1@gmail.com

RESPONSIBILITIES

Strong technical skills in complex website development including web-based applications.

Experience in system analysis, design, workflow architecture, development, testing and maintenance of web-based applications.

Can handle the overall design, development process with API Integrations in Angular.

OTHER SKILLS

Ability to explain with ease

Good Learner & Listener
Planning and execution
Creative Questioning

SKILLS

Front-End	Back-End	Databases
Angular	РНР	MySQL
Responsive Design	Node.JS	MongoDB
HTML, CSS, jQuery	-	-
Basic React.JS	-	-

LANGUAGES

GUJARATI, HINDI AND ENGLISH

EDUCATION

Gyanbharti College of Computer Science Junagadh.

March 2019

Bachelor of Computer Applications IT

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Alice, Ahmedabad, India

January 2021 to October 2021

Software Developer

- Revised, modularised and updated old code bases to modern development standards, reducing operating costs and improving functionality.
- Translated verbal customer requirements into written use cases and testable development stories.
- Designed and maintained streamlined, reusable and reliable code for use within distributed cloud environments.
- Planned and developed interfaces that simplified overall management and offered ease of use.

• Working with a large scale Angular project.

Noble DigVentures Junagadh, India

January 2020 to December 2020

Software Developer

- Collaborated with project managers to select ambitious, but realistic coding milestones on pre-release software project development.
- Worked in great technologies like PHP, ANGULAR, MySQL, Codeigniter, CSS, HTML, AJAX and JQUERY.
- Also worked as a Social media analyst.

WP Small Fix (Jannat Tech) Rajkot, India

April 2019 to December 2019

WordPress Developer

- Learning & working on PHP, WordPress and Responsive designing.
- The Team Lead assigned daily tasks, and work was to fulfill the client requirements.
- Like Adding new pages or updating existing ones. Updating the theme designs, updating the plugins. Solving errors. Making sure the WordPress websites are up-to-date.
- Learning CSS-Flexbox to solve responsive design problems.